[
    {
        "question": "Take the last letters of the words in \"Jose Ana Robert Mary\" and concatenate them.",
        "answer": "eaty"
    },
    {
        "question": "Take the last letters of the words in \"Laura Brian Patricia Sandra\" and concatenate them.",
        "answer": "anaa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Take the last letters of the words in \"David Maria Chris Carlos\" and concatenate them.",
        "answer": "dass"
    },
    {
        "question": "Take the last letters of the words in \"James Kevin Mark Nancy\" and concatenate them.",
        "answer": "snky"
    },
    {
        "question": "Take the last letters of the words in \"Jennifer Emily Jessica Anthony\" and concatenate them.",
        "answer": "ryay"
    },
    {
        "question": "Take the last letters of the words in \"Alex Melissa John Stephanie\" and concatenate them.",
        "answer": "xane"
    },
    {
        "question": "Take the last letters of the words in \"Daniel Juan Amanda Luis\" and concatenate them.",
        "answer": "lnas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Take the last letters of the words in \"Elizabeth Jason Mike Ashley\" and concatenate them.",
        "answer": "hney"
    },
    {
        "question": "Take the last letters of the words in \"Joe Lisa Linda Karen\" and concatenate them.",
        "answer": "eaan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Take the last letters of the words in \"Jorge Michael Sarah Michelle\" and concatenate them.",
        "answer": "elhe"
    }
]